<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>BitcoinZ Development Roadmap on BitcoinZ - Community-Driven Cryptocurrency</title><link>/en/</link><description>Recent content in BitcoinZ Development Roadmap on BitcoinZ - Community-Driven Cryptocurrency</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.143.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/en/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/privacy-policy/</guid><description>BitcoinZ Privacy Policy - Learn how we handle and protect your data</description></item><item><title>BitcoinZ and the Power of Privacy: Why It Matters and How zk-SNARKs Protect Your Rights</title><link>/en/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/privacy/</guid><description>Discover how BitcoinZ&amp;#39;s advanced privacy features and zk-SNARKs technology protect your financial freedom and rights in the digital age.</description></item><item><title>BitcoinZ: The Future of Scalable, Near-Zero-Fee Transactions</title><link>/en/scalability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/scalability/</guid><description>Discover how BitcoinZ achieves high scalability and near-zero transaction fees while maintaining true decentralization.</description></item><item><title>BitcoinZ: The Power of a True Community-Driven Coin</title><link>/en/community/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/community/</guid><description>Discover how BitcoinZ&amp;#39;s community-driven approach creates a truly decentralized and inclusive cryptocurrency ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Decentralization and Why BitcoinZ Excels</title><link>/en/decentralization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/decentralization/</guid><description>Discover how BitcoinZ embodies true decentralization principles, setting it apart from traditional financial systems and other cryptocurrencies.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/en/privacy-police/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/privacy-police/</guid><description>&lt;p>This website is a static site and does not collect or store any personal data. We do not use cookies, tracking scripts, or any other means of gathering information about our visitors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This website is run by the community and for the community. Any content posted is contributed voluntarily by community members. We do not monitor or track any user data.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you have any questions, please contact us through the community channels.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>/en/terms-off-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/terms-off-service/</guid><description>&lt;p>This website is provided as a community resource. By using this website, you agree to the following terms:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>No Warranty:&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
This website is provided on an &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; basis, without any warranty of any kind, express or implied.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>No Liability:&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
We shall not be liable for any damages arising from your use of this website or any reliance placed on its content.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Community Driven:&lt;/strong>&lt;br>
This website is created by and for the community. We do not guarantee the accuracy or completeness of any information shared here.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>