<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Where to Buy BitcoinZ on BitcoinZ - Community-Driven Cryptocurrency</title><link>/en/buy/</link><description>Recent content in Where to Buy BitcoinZ on BitcoinZ - Community-Driven Cryptocurrency</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.143.0</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/buy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WhiteBIT</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/central-exchange/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/central-exchange/</guid><description>A user-friendly European cryptocurrency exchange for trading digital assets</description></item><item><title>Changelly</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/changelly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/changelly/</guid><description>A fast and user-friendly exchange supporting wrapped BitcoinZ (wBTCZ) purchases with USD using Visa or MasterCard.</description></item><item><title>Cratex.io</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/cratex/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/cratex/</guid><description>A secure and easy-to-use cryptocurrency exchange platform supporting diverse trading pairs. Cratex.io focuses on accessibility and low fees, providing a seamless trading experience for both beginners and experienced traders.</description></item><item><title>Komodo Wallet</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/dex-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/dex-platform/</guid><description>A decentralized exchange platform offering secure and private trading of BitcoinZ with low fees and no KYC requirements</description></item><item><title>Liberty DEX</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/libertydex/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/libertydex/</guid><description>Community-driven decentralized exchange supporting instant BitcoinZ (BTCZ) purchases with top cryptocurrencies.</description></item><item><title>PancakeSwap</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/pancake_swap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/pancake_swap/</guid><description>A decentralized exchange on the Binance Smart Chain, offering liquidity pools and trading for wrapped BitcoinZ (wBTCZ). Wrapped BitcoinZ (wBTCZ) represents BitcoinZ (BTCZ) on the Binance Smart Chain, enabling seamless integration and use within the BSC ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Tip.cc</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/tipcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/tipcc/</guid><description>A cryptocurrency tipping bot for Discord and Telegram, enabling instant and fee-free transactions. Tip.cc supports BitcoinZ and other cryptocurrencies, fostering community engagement and adoption in social platforms.</description></item><item><title>TradeOgre</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/tradeogre/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/tradeogre/</guid><description>TradeOgre is a privacy-focused cryptocurrency exchange offering secure trading with a wide range of digital assets and minimal user requirements.</description></item><item><title>Xeggex</title><link>/en/buy/exchanges/safetrade/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/buy/exchanges/safetrade/</guid><description>A user-friendly cryptocurrency exchange providing secure and efficient trading for various digital assets. Xeggex offers low fees, no KYC requirements, and support for a wide range of trading pairs, making it an ideal platform for privacy-focused users.</description></item></channel></rss>